Guide to the Flora Williams French account books, 1858-1926.
French, Flora Williams account books, 1858-1926.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Flora Williams French account books, 1858-1926.
315
Flora Williams, French
1 cubic ft.,1 reel negative microfilm, 1 reel positive microfilm.
Account books, microfilm
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Account books of various Groton, New York, firms and insurance companies, personal accounts, and prescriptions and recipes for medicines. Also, microfilm of a Groton Iron Bridge Company daybook, 1877-1885.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Account books of various Groton, New York, firms and insurance companies, personal accounts, and prescriptions and recipes for medicines. Also, microfilm of a Groton Iron Bridge Company daybook, 1877-1885.
SUBJECTS
Names:
French, Flora Williams, collector.; Williams family; Groton Iron Bridge Company.
Subjects:
Medicine--Formulae, receipts, prescriptions.; Industries--New York (State)--Groton
Form and Genre Terms:
Account books.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- A. Insurance (William Williams & Co.)
  - 1. Wm, Williams & Co. Insurance Acct. Book, 1888-1895
  - 2. Mary B. Williams Insurance Acct. Book, 1896-1900
  - 3. Mary B. Williams Insurance Acct. Book, 1899-1903
  - 4. Mary B. Williams Expiration of Insurance, 1904-1908
  - 5. Wm Williams & Co. Expiration of Insurance, 1912-1916
  - 6. Wm Williams & Co. Insurance Acct. Book, 1903-1910
  - 7. Wm Williams & Co. Insurance Acct. Book, 1911-1919
  - 8. Wm Williams & Co. Expirations of Insurance, 1914-1917
  - 9. Wm Williams A Co. Expirations of Insurance, 1918-1922
- B. Groton Firms
  - 1. Groton Iron Bridge Co., Groton, N.Y.
    - a. Day Book, May 9, 1877- Aug. 31, 1885
    - b. Memorandum and Expense Acct. (Wa W. Williams), 1872
  - 2. Groton Manufacturing Co., Davenport, Iowa Acct. Book, l882
- C. Account Books
  - 1a. Carriage & Cabinet Makers Accounts, 1858
  - 1b. Carriage & Cabinet takers (coffins) Accounts, Undated
  - 2. N. Truable Dry Goods Memorandum, Groton, N.Y., May 1864
  - 3. K. B. Williams Account General Store, Groton, N.Y., around 1868
  - 4. W. W. Williams Memorandum & Accounts(Bridges ?), 1886-1887
  - 5a. Unidentified Account Book, 1858
  - 5b. Unidentified Account Book, Undated
- D. Groton, New York
  - 1. Enoch Bolles Personal Accounts, 1809-1821
  - 2a. Jennie Williams Personal Accounts and Notations, 1860
  - 2b. Jennie Williams Personal Accounts, 1912-1916
  - 3. J. Prank Weaver, Groton, N.Y.--School Book, 1875
  - E. R. Weaver, M.D. Prescriptions (p. 60-63) recipes for prescriptions.
  - Grace Weaver, Sec. and Treas. Sunday School
  - 4. W.W. Williams Personal Accounts, 1883
- E. Perrigo & Avery
  - 1. Perrigo & Avery, Notes & Bills Payable & Receivable, 1871-1884
  - 2. Perrigo & Avery, Notes & Bills Payable & Receivable, 1875-1884
  - 3. Invoice of Hotes and Accounts (containing 2 loose pages with list of notes.), 1885-1890
  - 4. Morton B. Lillians Assignees of Correspondence & Perrigo & Avery Copy, 1882-1899
  - Elisha Field Groton, N.Y. Book
  - 5. Morton B. Williams, assignee of Perrigo & Avery Expenditure Acct. Book, 1875-1879